# VERONIKA HARBACHOVA

Austin, TX | veronika.har@hotmail.com

# **Profile Summary**

A passionate web developer with vast cross-cultural experience and a proven record of problem-solving and optimization skills. Highly keen on lean code, user-friendly intuitive layouts and responsive designs that look great on any screen size.

## Education

#### **Certificate in Full-Stack Web Development**

CareerFoundry | 01/2019 - 11/2019

- 300+ hours of training/mentoring with industry leading Front-End and Senior Full-Stack Web Developer.
- Intensive project-based training program with a focus on Javascript, HTML, CSS and most prominent libraries, frameworks and tools;
- To see my skills in action, visit <a href="https://veronikaharbachova.netlify.com">https://veronikaharbachova.netlify.com</a>

#### **MA in Linguistics**

Dalian University of Technology | 09/2008 - 07/2011

#### **BA** in Linguistics

Belarusian State University | 09/2003 - 06/2008

## **Employment History**

### Wallenborn Transports S.A – Luxembourg, Luxembourg

*Supply Chain Specialist* | 02/2015 – 07/2016

- ✓ Provided customer service and account management for Qatar Airlines
  EU freight handling;
- ✓ Analyzed the company's internal S&OP software (AS-TRANS) and cooperated with an outsourced development team on its improvement;

## Lear Corporation – Shanghai, China

Supply Chain Specialist | 11/2013 - 06/2014

- ✓ Lead Logistics Network Optimization for China Seating: identified potential of 20-25% (\$300k annually) savings;
- ✓ Supported LEAR Malaysia Supply Chain recovery;

#### **Generation\_P** – Minsk, Belarus

XSLT developer / Assistant Team-Leader | 09/2007 - 08/2008

- ✓ Achieved full technical competency in 3 months without any prior experience (CVS repo; PAROS (POST/GET); Oxygen+Eclipse; XML etc);
- ✓ Assistant Team-Leader supervised team performing patch-and-release responsibilities and negotiated business solutions with foreign customers.

### **Professional Skills**

HTML

**CSS** 

**Javascript** 

Node.js

React.js

Redux

React Native

jQuery

**APIs** 

Photoshop

**Bootstrap** 

**Responsive Design** 

TDD

### **Toolkit**

**NPM** 

TypeScript

Sass

Jest/Enzyme

CodePen

GitHub

**Chrome Developer Tools** 

#### Soft Skills

Supportive

Empathetic

Approachable

Open-minded

Mission driven

Proactive

Adaptable

Collaborative

Open to feedback